"but she was too afraid
to hear the answer."
(Bernadette:)Oh, Amelia.
"So instead she asked if,
in the future,
Montana ever became a state."
(Amy:)In the 1800s
that was considered flirting.
(Raj:)I'm so sick of people
being mean on the Internet.
(Howard:)Well, I think the anonymity
makes everyone feel like
(Howard:)they can say things
they'd never say to your face.
(Sheldon:)Interesting.
(Sheldon:)I can't think of a single thing
(Sheldon:)I wouldn't say
to someone's face.
(Leonard:)Never noticed that about you.
You know what? A-At least
you guys did something.
You know, you-you had a theory,
(Leonard:)you wrote a paper,
(Raj:)you made
an actual contribution.
(Raj:)All guys like this do is just
stand on other people's work.
(Sheldon:)He's right.
(Sheldon:)I say we call this person back.
(Sheldon:)We've got no reason to hide.